Adeoye Adeola Oluwafunmike

64, Pepeye Layout, Oluwo Ibadan, Nigeria adeolafunmike@yahoo.com
08062605684

PERSONAL PROFILE

A well-mannered, articulate and hardworking customer care personnel who has been trained with experiences in providing a professional and efficient service to customer. Able to ensure high level of customer satisfaction and to exceed their expectations when it comes to customer care. Help full and approachable but also commercially minded and having the Ability to promote hotel facilities and maximize sale opportunity at all time. Taking enquiries, calls and also providing help and advice to customer using the company product and services. Aiming to build longtime relationship with customer.

SKILL AND COMPETENCES

Customer service skills

Having a professional and direct telephone manner with a clear and excellent voice, professionalism in telemarketing.

Managerial skill

Having been trained as a professional project manager to handle all forms of project in any sector.

Hospitality skills

Having a professional experience with an emphasis in hospitality and guest service.

Communication skills

Excellent listening and verbal communication skills, excellent spelling grammar and a flexible hand working attitude, able to work on own initiatives as well as part of a team. General insurance procedural and product knowledge.

Computer Skills

Experience in Microsoft software packages like words, Excel, power point, access.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Konga Online Shopping Mall

Call Center Agent (Inbound) May 2016 - Dec. 2016

Job Role:

- Respond to inbound calls
- Document customers complain and requests
- Escalate customers issues where necessary
- Use of the company's CRM tools
- Calling of customers for promos and discount (outbound)

Mannastores Online Limited

Customer Service Executive (Sept 2015 - April 2016).

Job Role:

- Receive calls from customer
- Respond the complaints and customer request
- Assist customer to prepare invoices for online purchases.
- Surf the internet for cheap stores in UK and USA
- Calculating the weight of goods delivered by the courier service and also the individual weight
- Reconcile customers payment with invoices
- Respond to live chat
- In charge of company's petty cash account

Environmental department Oredo Local Government Corper (NYSC)

2014 - 2015

Job Role:

- Monitoring of the environmental sanitation exercise in the state
- Attending to issues and complain concerning environmental issues
- Assistant in the supervising and issuing of burial permit to people
- All other administrative job given by the superior

Daktad Suite and Events Centre

2010 - 2011

Receptionist (Industrial Training)

Job Role:

- Welcoming guest in the hotel in a polite, friendly and helpful manner
- Deals with late arrival and early checkouts
- Check out departing guest using the hotel accounting system
- Taking payment from guest in form of cash
- Answering telephone enquiries promptly, professionally and transferring calls on
- Being on point of contact for guest should they have any queries
- Deals with and resolving customers complaint
- Keeping up to date on all hotel products, services, pricing and promotional offer.
- Maximizing sales revenue through up selling and marketing programmes

Dusmar Presidential Hotel

2008

Recptionist (Siwes training)

Job Role:

- Assist in Welcoming guest in the hotel in a polite, friendly and helpful manner
- Assist in dealing with late arrival and early checkouts
- Check out departing guest using the hotel accounting system
- Answering telephone enquiries promptly and professionally and transfering calls on
- Being on point of contact for guest should they have any queries
- Deals with and resolving customers complaint

- Keeping up to date on all hotel products, services, pricing and promotional offer.
- Maximzing sales revenue through up selling and marketing programmes
- Working in other department in accordance to the training

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

Telemarketing Diploma May 2015 Huston Texas U.S.A. Certified Customer service/Telesales Professional Gennesaret Resources Nigeria Limited April 2015 Portharcourt-Aba road Nigeria Certificate in Basis Health and Safety management HSE Mar. 2014 - Mar. 2015 National Youth Service Corp Edo State NYSC Discharge Certificate River State University Of Science and Technology Oct.2014 In affiliation with Luxurynet International Ict Academy Certified Project Management Professional (P.M.P) 2013 **Enterpreneurship Development Centre** The Federal Polythecnic Ilaro chapter Certified Venue Decorator **EDUCATION** The Federal Polytechnic Ilaro 2011 - 2013 Hospitality Management (Higher National Diploma) The Federal Polytechnic Ilaro 2008 - 2010 Hotel and catering Management (National Diploma) Baptist Girl's College Idi-aba Abeokuta 2002 - 2008 Secondary School certificate God's Gift Children School, Abeokuta 1996 - 2002 First School Leaving Certificate

BIO DATA

Date Of Birth: August 28 1990

Nationality: Nigerian
State Of Origin: Ogun-State
Marital Status: Married

LANGUAGE

English, Yoruba

INTEREST

Reading, surfing the web, Singing, Watching Soccer

REFERENCE

Available upon Request